sup everyone team was only five with a
very special video today so I said hey
all of you have been asking me so I'm
gonna do it I'm gonna upload my very
first ever let's play of a video game
and I thought more of a better way than
do it with Overwatch it's something a
lot of people really wanna do I never
played this game myself but yeah why the
[ __ ] not
I'll just going throw myself into a
quick game because as I said I've never
played before so yeah let's do this
[ __ ] this is a pure luck I think 30 or
so characters I'm not I don't [ __ ]
know to be honest I'm not only know what
skills do you pick I know which is good
or bad out I might pick this [ __ ] I
mean orange hair purple and yellow color
scheme it's like like that [ __ ] from
Sonic under that you know I'm tired like
Max girlfriend like mini Latoya that
[ __ ] that's really [ __ ]
yeah so yeah that started going to
[ __ ] new Barney or some [ __ ] don't
know what that is gonna rock pick this
characters like [ __ ] [ __ ] sock on the
ground okay we we got Hanzo
I heard he's okay no we don't soldiers
had six out hood he's good he's not
gonna call of duty player so anyone can
play I shoulda party Kmart I kick ass
and call of duty I don't get [ __ ] ok
this team looks pretty [ __ ] and if you
ask me
so fine no play this [ __ ] I never you
played Overwatch that's right now played
this game so forgive me if I may seem
like a no I dare I will because as I
said I'm good at shooter game so let me
go into this [ __ ] down there we go boom
suck
come on I just want to play the game how
long is this gonna take 30 seconds I
gotta wait 30 [ __ ] seconds for this
[ __ ] oh my God
the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] oh my God damn
can't break that [ __ ] oh my God
hey it's cold what's that dog I don't
know what that I don't know what the
[ __ ] that is
I'm away this [ __ ] is oh damn I got
this [ __ ] so what what am I doing I
suppose just kill people
okey then let's do it what the [ __ ]
push your minds what the [ __ ]
damn essence a [ __ ] what the [ __ ] I
don't know what I'm doing
am I supposed to be killing people okay
pillow wait I gotta get here I'm winning
already is this what I'm supposed to do
damn I'm doing good
Oh when I passed Kim so what the [ __ ]
what my [ __ ] and oh my God what do I
do
this is [ __ ] insane oh my God I got a
[ __ ] lock beat some ass now [ __ ]
oh my God what my powders doing this is
[ __ ] up
okay so everyone's going in there locked
[ __ ] for some reason now and get
[ __ ] more damn [ __ ] get out there
stupid [ __ ]
can you guys talk not kill people oh my
God am I the only one hitting people
oh my God what the [ __ ] damn boy the
[ __ ] was he doing he came a transforming
[ __ ] can I do that
I'll [ __ ] kill that [ __ ] I'm here
for oh this is insane
oh my God what do I do against Pamela's
what the [ __ ] do I do against that [ __ ]
kill them are you [ __ ] stupid are you
[ __ ] stupid this is this is just
insane I can't believe it I'm paired
with knows a pair what [ __ ] knows
are you kidding me oh my God this is
just insane they cannot kill one person
this is just sick insane am I gonna have
to like go in there with Hawking all to
me and save everyone mother
this [ __ ] sang back you told what the
[ __ ] that [ __ ] deal is just someone
flying up there you can fly in this game
stupid [ __ ] oh my God get out here all
could ever want kill it all these
[ __ ] oh my God got you too [ __ ] oh
my God office shot kill everyone
there's it same get on the objective oh
my [ __ ] God
all right here again I was just killing
everyone
oh my God oh [ __ ] bye [ __ ]
keep up the time I'm a doggie this is
just I got [ __ ] sweat oh my God oh my
God
first the [ __ ] black I'll give [ __ ] I
got this [ __ ] what the [ __ ] is this
pose even though I can she of course I
can't he's a [ __ ] chill the game
could kill all these [ __ ] oh I got
your ass [ __ ] this is just [ __ ] up
but we your [ __ ] play this game I
don't know
oh my God I don't know what the [ __ ]
class this is just insane oh I'll play
is that [ __ ] [ __ ] don't was this guy
dude [ __ ] like [ __ ] ballsy [ __ ]
that's gasps [ __ ] I mean come the [ __ ]
on this is just [ __ ] up up stupid
[ __ ]
warm up on 0 I thought you were supposed
to play this [ __ ] game rod and Mario
dude hey that guy oh my [ __ ] God
oh my God hit that fly [ __ ] what the
[ __ ] I can't keep that [ __ ] no one's
gonna resurrect me oh my God I don't
know what the [ __ ] I'm doing I'm just
switching Radwin out [ __ ]
oh my God mocking [ __ ] service it's
not [ __ ] time how long they have to
[ __ ] take is it that how for some
people to understand how to play this
game oh my [ __ ] God oh my God you can
oh one hit back out there
this is yah I'm killing this [ __ ] yeah
yeah you better run [ __ ] oh now you're
gonna shoot me again okay I'll get I'm
good I'm Taylor five [ __ ] get down here
oh my [ __ ] God I found you [ __ ] oh
he's a ball that [ __ ] get off this [ __ ]
I'll kill all of you [ __ ] rape you in
the ass [ __ ] oh my God that's a [ __ ]
up there this is insane get on the
objective oh my God oh [ __ ] oh my get on
my [ __ ] I'm killing everyone what are
my partners at with all my partners oh
my God well what the hell what will
those [ __ ]
this is insane damn [ __ ] oh my God
this is just [ __ ] up oh my God come on
oh he idea focal
you can go through into this game oh
[ __ ] no come on is it that how to not
win well my partner's at [ __ ] this I'm
doing this myself group the [ __ ] up
[ __ ] are you kidding me oh now he comes
okay come on [ __ ]
I'll kill you [ __ ] Jeff here weak-ass
[ __ ] I don't need you kaffir
oh my God doing everything off of this
[ __ ] this is insane
so this is just [ __ ] I'm doing
everything
boom [ __ ] come on move your ass [ __ ] I
can't [ __ ] see oh my God I got home
to me was that no doesn't make me win oh
my [ __ ] God I'll kill that late [ __ ]
all ultimate oh she I killed someone
Oh y'all kill you too [ __ ] oh my God
I'm gonna play the game I'll kill you
too oh [ __ ] I'm killing everyone get out
of here [ __ ] oh my [ __ ] God four
kills in a row [ __ ] come on come on oh
[ __ ] oh my God oh [ __ ] I [ __ ] won
play of the game
come on [ __ ] I kill four [ __ ] come
on come on who the [ __ ] is that [ __ ] are
you kidding me I killed everyone
first I play know what I killed everyone
fans in time oh my God
damn [ __ ] you can't be my ass
I'll be your ass come on
I'm not vote for him I'll give her
another need money my vote
damn I'm good that was insane [ __ ] oh
my God like comment and subscribe if you
want to see more of this [ __ ] cuz oh my
God I'm good
lates [ __ ] oh my God
timber five out